You're listening to the AI Native Dev,
brought to you by Tessa.
Welcome back, and it's time for another
monthly recap on the AI Native
Developer. My name is Simon Maple.
Hello, guy Podarney, or guy Poe?
Guy Poe.
And so, we're going to cover the
sessions that happened in in September.
Um first of all, of course, you had a
session with Tamar
on Enterprise AI. Really really
insightful.
Tamar is amazing. We'll cover some
topics that we talked about uh Glean and
Enterprise Search, uh but also a lot of
learning of how to build this type of AI
product.
Yeah, very interesting. And then I spoke
with uh Omar Rosenbaum, also a
co-founder of Swimm. Really interesting
about how you can use AI to keep your
documentation up to date, and also
inform developers of when they're
touching code that has documentation
associated with it. Really insightful
sessions there. And then a fellow
podcast host, Caleb Sima, you spoke with
him.
Uh
Caleb is is excellent. That wasn't a
surprise. He does host the AI Security
podcast. And surprise, surprise, he
talked about AI Security on it, and had
really good conversations. I think that
was maybe like a bit more elaborate,
opinionated in that conversation. It is
the topic that is uh very near and dear
to my heart, which is AI and Search.
Oh, two geeks talking about security.
That must have been a laugh.
was it was a delight. It was a real
laugh.
It was a
big big laugh fest. That was uh
that was all going down. Uh it was
actually like a positive leaning view on
on AI Security, but really enjoyed that
conversation. We'll share a few
highlights here. Uh and yeah, Caleb's
awesome, as always.
Amazing. And to to round off the month,
we had we had Felipe Aguirre Martinez,
who was actually on earlier this week in
with his session. And yeah,
Felipe reached out to us to just to chat
about various things that we were
talking about in the podcast, and I
explored various things that he's doing,
and learn the whole we had him on the
podcast and he came over to London to to
chat with us and give that podcast all
about how he develops using AI such that
he's actually trying as much as he can
rather than writing code but to actually
build an application through prompts and
specifications. So, really interesting.
We'll cover all those in more depth
about our learnings and various topics.
But for now, Guy,
I absolutely love talking with you. I've
got someone who I think is that that
little bit more professional, little bit
more eloquent. So, Guy, if you wouldn't
mind leaving for I don't know, 5 to 10
minutes. Yeah, we're just not recording.
I know, but Guy, we're going to we're
going to try something new. And this
isn't anything on you. This is just an
experiment we're trying. So, I'll
indulge you, but I'm going to call you
later.
Okay. Yeah, if you leave this room and
go to the building next door, that
that's where HR is. Um so, so uh joining
me is uh is Ben Galbraith. Uh Ben,
please uh join. And Guy, yeah, make sure
that the door fully closes so we can
have a proper So, there we go. There we
go. Ben, have a seat. Welcome. Welcome
to the AI Naked Podcast. How are you?
I'm great, Simon. Great to be here. I'm
flattered and I don't think I'm as
charismatic as you've let people to
believe. So, hopefully it won't be too
big of a
Well, we'll judge you over the next 10
minutes and then make a decision based
on that, shall we?
Oh, that makes it all better.
So, Ben, tell us a little bit about your
illustrious career till now.
All right. All right. I'll give you a
Should I feel like a 20 25-minute
survey? Absolutely. I can do that.
I'll just give you a quick a quick
highlight reel. I've been professionally
developing software my whole career. I
got started early. I I think I started
professional development when I was 12,
left high school and secondary school.
What do you call secondary school here?
Midway through to work for Easter
full-time and just did a lot of stuff
since then, working on top of major
platforms and eventually working to make
those platforms better. Uh some of the
highlights of that time period include
uh reading product design and and uh
engineering for Walmart's global
e-commerce stuff. Uh I worked at Mozilla
doing dev tools for Mozilla. Then I
worked and went to a Palm. Palm had this
big swing at this moment in time, maybe
you remember, where they wanted to make
the web the operating system that that
led on mobile. And I was part of that.
I don't want to call it a misadventure,
but it was
Uh but I had a great time. And uh and
then I uh
I was part of this thing called Ajaxian
that was uh part of uh leading the Web
2.0 and Ajax movement of the era. It was
a conference series, too. That was a
blast. And most recently I've been at
Google. Uh I was at Google for about 8
years. I uh led product and design for
this thing called Firebase, which had
this vision to sort of remove all the
toil of app development for developers
so you can just focus on what made your
app special. And I spent most of my time
at Google on the Chrome team, working on
the web platform and making the web
better. That was amazing, working with
just incredibly talented product
managers and engineers and designers,
working to make Chromium better, working
to make V8 better, media codecs, which
is just doing a FaceTime with my family,
which I do all the time. They're still
in the US right now. And I just dropped
me how amazing codecs have become. And
it was real pleasure to work with some
of those guys. And and a bunch of other
stuff at Google, driving initiatives
like Core Web Vitals and Baseline.
Anyway, that's kind of a highlight reel
and enough of what I've been up to.
That is a real Most people don't do half
of that in their entire career, Ben.
That's That's That sounds amazing.
You're like a flattery machine. I want
to be on the podcast more often than
this.
Just wait for my next question, Ben.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
So, Google, that great company Google,
great employer. They really look after
their staff, don't they? What would make
you
Where is this going?
on Earth What possessed you to
go from an an amazing company like
Google, leading so many different
technologies and and such an amazing
research group, sunny, glorious
California. What made you leave all that
and come to rainy, cold London to work
for this
Yeah, he's gone.
work for guy powerful people
for a startup called Test All. What on
Earth would make you do that, Ben?
Well, the way you put it now, I'm having
second thoughts. about that.
I I'm saying it myself, and I'm
questioning I'm questioning myself, too.
That was a great question.
This is turning into a therapy session.
I do have the weather conversation with
my wife from time to time.
Really? Yeah.
That's maybe the most painful part.
that you're bringing across the pond in
end of fall winter. That's when the UK
really shines.
I first we'll talk about relocation
logistics in a minute.
Getting to the Google thing, yeah. I've
been thinking about doing a startup
again for a while. I've done a a bunch
of startups, and Google's an amazing
place.
But, 8 years is a long time, and I've
been feeling like it's time for me to
get out and do something different. And
actually, we I had this funny moment. I
I don't think I mentioned in my survey.
Guy and I have been friends for ages. We
crossed paths early in in my career when
I was at Walmart and he was at Akamai,
and it was fun to see his journey at
Snyk, and I had the chance to check in
with him regularly along the way. And we
had this funny moment in February of
this year where I texted Guy and I said,
"Hey, I'm I'm thinking about leaving
Google to do a startup." And and I
described what I had in mind using
principles that we now call "I needed
development." And he replied with this
sort of wry emoji smile saying, "We
should probably talk." And I had made a
change, too. And at first, I just felt
like, "Yeah, it sounds great, but
London. I don't know that I could do
London." And then I came out in the
summer, you remember, and got to spend
time with Guy and meet the team here at
Tessol. I was blown away. I was blown
away at learning more about Guy's vision
and just meeting you and the rest of the
Tessol team. Just seemed to be to be
fair, maybe present company excluded.
The rest of the team
Yeah.
pretty amazing folk, and and I walked
away from that. I came here feeling like
I'll I'll at least have this moment with
Guy and explain to him why this is too
big of a change for me right now, and
maybe I'll see if I can be an advisor to
the company or something. And then I
left that visit feeling like, "Wow, I
have to be a part of this team." And I
was fortunate that you and and and Guy
and the rest of the team maybe felt a
little similarly about me being a good
fit. And then I had the difficult
conversation with my family. But, I have
to explain we've had a history of
adventures as a family. We lived in Hong
Kong for 2 months when I first started
at Google and loved that. We still talk
about it all the time. And when I talked
to my family about both sort of the
professional opportunity and just the
chance to have another family adventure,
be honest, we all took a leap and felt
like this could be a really special
thing for us. I did not talk about the
weather with my family. We were looking
at like expat videos on YouTube and the
weather came up over and over again. My
wife turned and looked at me and said,
"This was not part of the deal, but I'm
sure it'll be fine."
Yeah, yeah. And very briefly, cuz I
think the guy's coming back from HR now.
And they're bored. The number of times
the number of complaints he has for me,
they're bored. They just turn them away.
So, we'll be back in 80 seconds. Um
if you if you were to if you were to
kind of like think of a couple of things
that have surprised you or that like
that you've been, you know, super pumped
about learning and and doing it at at
Tessol, what were those couple of
things?
You know, two big surprises so far.
First one isn't at Tessol. It just has
to do with London itself. I've long said
that I thought New York City was one of
my favorite cities, maybe my favorite
place in the world. And uh I've been to
London many times through the course of
my career. I had folks that I managed in
London when I was at Google.
But there's something about being here
now, cuz I spend the most of my time
here in London. I have loved the city. I
love the English countryside far more
than I expected. And that's been a huge
surprise. I love it here.
Beginning with Tessol, the other thing
that's been surprising is, you know, I
knew from my visit in London how amazing
the Tessol team were. Present company me
maybe being the exception, but I've been
really surprised at how many developers
I've met who share the vision that we've
been talking about, that you and Guy
have been talking about in the AI Native
Dev podcast. That people have seen this
exciting possibility of going further
than using AI as a sort of code
completer and AI co-pilot to rethink
software from the ground up. And you
know, it feels like it's in the water
and we're all sort of asking ourselves,
how would we rethink the way that we
build software? And I feel like at
Tessol, that's been maybe my biggest
surprise is how many people are rooting
for this movement that we're trying to
create and really want to be a part of
it.
Yeah, I I I I really resonates with me
actually, cuz I was at a user group
presenting last last week and I was a
little unsure as to when I'm giving
these messages of or talking about where
the future's going and people were
actually quite receptive to it. Cuz I I
thought there'd be like levels of fear
or levels of uncertainty, but that
people were actually keen to learn more
and keen to
want to get engaged with the existing AI
dev tools and wanting to explore them.
But yeah, I that really resonates with
me. I see guys actually coming coming
back to me. So yeah,
so yeah and then wonderful to hear all
the amazing things that you've said
about Diapo
and yeah, we'll chat later and to the to
the listeners
we'll probably hear from Ben maybe in
the future as well, maybe running a
session or two.
Ben, great to see, great to looking
forward to working with
Don't don't get too comfortable.
You guys done yet?
Yeah, how about
What is the number?
If I had a penny every time you told me
that guy.
Cheers, Ben.
This month you released a really
interesting blog about how AI and tools
can be positioned. Tell us a little bit
about that.
So yeah, I had a chance to to write down
finally this sort of mental model I have
about AI solutions that I have been
stewing on for a good year plus a year
and a half around how to think about
this sort of messy world of AI
solutions. And it's true for the dev
space, but it's also true for for other
domains. And what I've seen as an
investor and
I don't want to repeat the blog post
here, so you should check it out on the
Tesla blog, but at a high level it talks
about how AI solutions can be mapped
across these two dimensions. One is
change, so how much do I need to change
the way I work to be able to use this
product and the other is trust, which is
how much do I need to trust it to get it
right for it to be useful to me. So let
me just give like a couple of examples.
The change trust the Synthesia is a good
example of it. Synthesia is a text to
video solution on it, so create videos
with text. That's an entirely different
way of creating video and question about
whether you can just use it as a
co-pilot the way we create videos today.
It's a total reinvention of how you're
doing it, which gives them an
opportunity to just entirely
replace all sorts of bottlenecks and
problems that they had. But they but
it's a big change. Like the people
involved in producing the video, a
training video or media video, whatever
in a in a company, need to do things
that are entirely different. You have to
rethink the supply chain. Some people
get startled by it. Maybe it's not the
same skill set you want in the team. So
it's a big change, but really I think
big kind of disruption opportunities and
new startups are coming into that space
and an opportunity to really rethink the
problems in in in a domain. The other
axis is one of trust. And so how much do
I need to trust it to get it right even
if you didn't require me to change how I
work? I think the simplest example there
is the robo taxis. And so if you pull
out an Uber app or something like that
and you call a taxi and you it arrives,
the car arrives, you get in, you get
dropped off at a location, you get off.
It's the same experience whether a human
drove that car or if it's AI driving it.
And so very little change in how you
work, but massive amounts of trust,
right? Like you need to trust that this
car will will get you there alive.
Yeah. And so I think that's a good
example. So those are like two
dimensions and when you think about AI
solutions you can plot them to say how
much change is required to get this, how
much trust is required to get this. And
what you find is that the tools that get
the most adoption today are at the
bottom left. They're in that sort of low
change, low trust, right? So co-pilot
for instance for development. You're
just typing in a letter. It plugs into
how you code today.
You can eyeball the result and see if
it's correct or not. It has some
security implications. You don't review
it as well. But but you can
use it very quickly. So just as long as
it works often enough, it just makes you
better. No reason not to use it. But but
it's it's incremental. It doesn't
entirely address any problems. It
doesn't rethink the workflows on it. But
still that's where we see the most sort
of action in things that can help you
today. No change, no trust required. And
then of course the last quadrant is that
sort of top right, which is what we call
the AI native future, which you hear us
here talking about AI native development
and spec centric and all those things
like that's a far right. So anyways,
that's the mental model in a nutshell
and I have more details, more examples,
more how to think about yourself and
charting your journey between those on
the
That got shared a lot. Tell us a little
bit about the feedback. Any points that
kind of made you think further about it?
Yeah, it was fun to see I as I said I've
been brewing this for a while now. So I
got a lot of feedback over the year from
smart people around it. So it was good
to get a lot of kind of response. People
liking it and reposting is fine. You get
some positive comments on LinkedIn is
all nice, but I think a better
indication is when someone on their own
initiative posts about it talks about
how it works. What I found most useful
is that people talked about their
domains and how how this applies to
them. So I'm happy to hear that they're
using it and they find it useful. And I
also liked that in the same week just
after just before I think Microsoft and
Salesforce both had big AI
announcements. It was nice to see how
they both chose different path. There
was Microsoft co-pilot pages which
really uh tries to create this sort of
funky way in which people can
collaboratively edit the document.
Multiple people each with AI assistance
edit the document and maybe combine the
apps. So I think that's firmly the
change path. You look at it it feels
weird. It feels odd if you think about
it and maybe they got it right, maybe
they didn't, but it's definitely a
change from how we edit today. And
Salesforce launching this agent
foresight with automated agents, which
is very much the trust path. It's like
same work, you open the ticket and it's
just instead of a human fulfilling that
ticket, it might be an AI agent, but you
have to trust that agent got it right.
You have to have that element. And so
anyways, it was another a nice timely
demonstration of how there are different
ways to tackle using AI to improve our
kind of efficiency, our lives, how we do
things.
Yeah, absolutely. And actually when I
was doing the session with Felipe and we
were looking through a number of
different tools, it made me think about
I'm starting to think about this now in
the in the quadrants about where things
sit. And I And as I mentioned to Ben, I
gave a session where I was walking
through a number of different tools last
week in London. And I was trying to work
out where they should be positioned. And
it was interesting cuz Felipe, when he
talked about using things like Claude,
he wanted to then take that code and put
it into an IDE to play with it
afterwards and do things like that. And
it's interesting whereby what we see is
the evolution of the tools we use isn't
just like one big leap and we're there.
Very often, there's a big step of
innovation, and then people work out how
we can actually then pull that back a
little bit into our IDE. So, it's
interesting to see something like
pushing into that Claude projects, for
example. And then there's this cursor
space whereby you can have that
conversation and it does it all for you
in your IDE. And it just brings it
closer to what we're more comfortable
with till that step to the next place
actually seems smaller. So, yeah, really
interesting kind of positioning things
more like that now.
And I I love that. I think the the
opportunity in the change track is to
rethink
our fundamental assumptions. What would
make you change your mind? Now that in
our context, now that machines can write
code, now that machines can fill in the
gaps of what you didn't tell them in the
requirements. Yeah, what does that open
up, right? What opportunities, what
problems can we rethink? And then how
exactly those things should become
reality, that's a process. So, that
absolutely resonates with how people are
doing
it. So, try it out and they learn to do
it with their eyes. It's okay, but
that's
I can't use that yet because like I need
to maybe leave my IDE and then, you
know, maybe that's the in the Claude
example, right? You can go to the web
and you can write a bunch of things and
you can build your application. But
people was like, "Yeah, but I There's
all these other things I need to do and
they're in my IDE. Okay, can I bring
that experience to me
for the IDE?" So, I think I think it's
awesome and I love to see that
evolution. And we we do our bit over
here.
Mhm.
But but it's good to see.
So, so let's step out of your comfort
zone now of AI. Let's talk about
security guy. If you're unsure, feel
free to make it up. What are the
concerns that were brought up over this
last month around AI security? I know we
had Tamar, and obviously Caleb, whose
session was around AI security. But
there were some interesting mentions in
Tamar's session.
Certainly not here. Maybe you can take
the kid out of the security industry,
but you can't take the security industry
out of a kid.
I was quite happy actually some have
security-related conversations on it. We
had the one with Caleb, which was
clearly about security that was
designed, that was by planning. But even
the conversation with Tamar, security
was a big piece of it. Primarily because
of access to data. And so the thing to
understand is in the world of LLMs, as
Caleb phrased it very well, there's no
separation between the control plane and
the data plane. And maybe think about
that SQL. In SQL, you have the command
select from table name from something,
that's the structure of it. And then
there is this like where field equals
something that is text. And you know
that, you know, there's something that
is text, that is the data, that is the
data plane versus the control plane,
that is the command. In LLM world, you
don't have that. You just give one
instruction, there's no field, there's
no structure on it, it's just language
like like we humans do, right? And and
as a result of that, the system can't
delineate very clearly what is it that
you said that is data and is control.
And effectively there's no solution to
that today, right? You know, I think
Caleb highlighted that and I think
that's I've not yet seen anyone to to
really devise a solution that is
deterministic around that.
Yeah.
And so that leaves you in this awkward
position when you're offering tools to
enterprise companies because access to
data is very important. And Glean has an
interesting approach to that is that the
way that they approached it is the LLM
actually doesn't know any of the data.
So the LLM only interacts with the
control plane. It is trained on the
systems, how do I go to an HR system and
able to can extract information from it,
or how do I go to to to Zoom or to Gong
and extract some recorded conversations
from it. But then when the user asks to
do that, the actions are being done
using rag. So only the relevant data per
the permissions of this user in a
traditional authorization are being
done, that's brought into the
conversation, and now only in the
context of this session the LLM knows
this is the data. And so because an LLM
never knows the broader data outside of
that sort of context, and because
fetching the data is done with the
user's permissions, they eliminate I
should say that with an asterisk, right?
Or greatly reduce the risk of of data
leaking into the system and a user being
able to access data Yeah. That they
don't have, which I thought was really
interesting. So that was I think we
talked about all sorts of things
security and we should talk a bit about
generating code and whether it's secure
or not, but I think that was the
connecting point between the tomorrow
episode and Caleb. And I think it's
something for us to truly internalize
when we think about security and LLMs.
Yeah, absolutely, cuz it's not you're
not allowing the LLM to effectively
determine whether it is or isn't allowed
to use that data. You're only providing
it with the data it's allowed to use for
that request, which I think is
absolutely core. Now Caleb, with Caleb's
session of course, you asked you
blatantly asked the question, can an LLM
provide code whereby there are no
insecurities at all? And I love the
answer he gave, which is based on the
success of your previous company, "Guy,
no, it cannot produce secure code all
the time."
I was just hopeful, wasn't I? Caleb was
like, "Guy, you know, can you just can
you give me an answer? Do LLMs generate
secure code or not?"
Um yeah, I think maybe part of it is
indeed the the tongue-in-cheek. If the
humans write secure code, as we showed,
there's definitely a need for for
verifying that. With Caleb, one of the
many things I liked about how he phrases
things is he just has a sort of concrete
approach to thinking about security on
it that's very practical. So he says,
"LLMs are trained on human code. Human
code, as we know, is not terribly
secure, definitely not by and large. And
so why would we think that generation of
code that is trained on that will be
more secure. So, above and beyond all
the fanciness of did it understand the
code not correct like just the marching
orders were all with insecure code. And
so, I think that was okay and I think
it's it's just a simple understanding
that we shouldn't assume that code is
secure. And then it was like there was a
layer of optimism on top of that and I
think the two takeaways that I have are
one
it will get better cuz we do still
incentivize the LLM when we do identify
this code is good and this code is bad.
Treat this code as something that is
better and a bunch of the companies that
train on enterprise code bases allow
their users to do that as well. So, say
hey these are like golden pull requests
they're very good. And the second, which
I actually personally am more excited
by, is that if the machine writes the
code once you get into like autonomous
workflows, then you can really embed uh
automation of the testing into the
development process. So, it's not so
much about whether the LLMs produce more
or less secure code, but it's more about
the fact that machines are not lazy. And
I don't mean developers lazy in like a
accusatory fashion. Well, there's some
guy saw some Yeah, no amongst the team
But I don't mean, you know, accusatory I
just mean we're humans, right? And so,
we we we don't always deliver on on all
of these toil pieces that we need to do.
So, machines are are different, right?
Like machines do continue to run those
and so, we can run security tests, we
can fix vulnerabilities, we can do those
thoroughly.
Mhm. Yeah, and
combining a couple of things there to
talk about uh another topic which is
really about how LLMs combined with
other ways of doing things, whether it's
static analysis, whether it's the
authorization that we talked about with
Tamas' session. It seems that we need to
really clearly recognize we need to
combine it with various other
technologies or ways of working whereby
the actual overall result is either far
better or far more consistent execution
after execution. So,
there are a couple there are a couple of
topics here. One around static analysis,
which I know the Swim guys there's a
really actually good quote from the Swim
team. They asked,
"If you didn't use static analysis,
determining which areas of code related
to which areas of documentation, how
accurate would you be? How consistent
would you be about saying this piece of
code change actually requires changes to
these other pieces of documentation?"
And I almost said 80% of the output that
came out of an LLM only approach to that
would be noise. And actually it was the
static analysis, the creating of the
AST, which then the LLM used to
determine and that linking between code
and and documentation. That's what
actually creates that far better
experience and I think we'll see that
more and more as we recognize what LLMs
are good at, where they need assistance,
and so forth.
Yeah, no I love that. That's like
hallucination prevention, right?
Yeah, exactly. Similar to what Dez was
talking about with with Finn.
Absolutely.
You have some element of ground truth to
to keep the LLMs in in check. Yeah, I
think that was a very good insight on it
and I think a good reminder of it. And I
think we know we had similar
conversations with Caleb around how
static analysis plays a role in the
security side and it's interesting to
think we talked before about this change
in trust and it's interesting to think
about on one hand how do we get
predictability, how do we get
determinism so that things are not
noise. And in other cases, how do we
accept the lack of predictability for
value and the conversation we had there
is we do static analysis today of code,
say it's sneak and and other solutions,
and they are they're more deterministic.
So, they would find if you scan the same
code with the same sort of rule set on
it, you're going to get the same set of
results.
But with LLMs, if you scan them, they
don't act that way. Like they're they're
statistical. So, you might scan the same
code 10 times and maybe eight times out
of those 10, it finds a vulnerability,
and twice it doesn't. Maybe sometimes it
hallucinates a false positive. You You
can talk about what's better and what's
not, but I think a good question is also
like, how do we adapt? How do we change
our methodology to that reality, right?
When you run a scan, and you say, "Hey,
this is vulnerability free." If you run
it with something that's statistical,
can you make that statement? Can you
give it the stamp of approval? Do you
need to scan it 10 times now? How do you
work with that? And I think the good
challenge from Caleb was, it depends on
how valuable it is.
Yeah.
If in those eight times, it gives you
massively accurate results, maybe you
make peace with that, right? And you
just before you need to bless it, you
scan it three times, and you think,
"That's good enough statistics, and I
and I will give it a stamp of approval."
Yeah.
So, I think this notion of dealing with
uh unpredictability of these systems is
really interesting.
Yeah.
Uh and so, you you made a good point of
how do we make them more predictable?
That's one part, that's the trust piece.
How do we know that they got it right?
And then, the other side is the change
piece.
Yeah.
So, it's I I I think both of those
elements are really interesting.
Yeah, and there's a couple of other
things that actually stood out from the
session that you did with Tamar. Uh one
of which is combining types of AI. So,
for example, with Glean, they have
obviously a search as well.
Uh and and it's that combination of
symbolic AI with LLMs that actually
creates that really strong power.
Another thing actually, just on the
point of the consistency and getting in
that non-determinism, uh Tamar
mentioned, you know,
when you as soon as you look to the
enterprise, there are CIOs that are
spending huge amounts of money on
software.
Yeah.
If they ask a question today, and they
ask a question tomorrow, or even later
that day, they're they're paying that
money, and they want the same answer.
And it's whether we change our mindset
in terms of understanding there's power
in this LLM, but you got to expect that
variance in in determinism, or whether
we need to add some level of consistency
in as part of that to say, "Okay, we're
going to use LLMs, but we want to track
answers to make sure that we're giving
consistency." There's work to be done
one way or the other in there.
and it's how do you like it people pay
money for this, It'd better work.
So, that that rounds up another monthly
guy. Can you believe? It's What is it
now? Is it October?
Yeah.
What is it 20 Is it 2024 still? I can't
It's in October now. Time continues to
be a blurry.
Oh, gosh. Yeah.
It's fun to actually have those moments
and look back at the month. Sometimes
the month goes by in such a
such a rush. I don't stop a moment.
Bit of reflection.
It could be someone is like terrible
with my like routines or my wife is
terrible with is a excellent at
That was That was close. That was close,
guys. I wish I think I might leave that
in the edit. Just to Just Yeah,
absolutely. Yeah.
excellent at having a routine sitting
down at the end of the week and
summarizing what uh which is kind of
taken from this week. You're like, I'm
jealous about that.
Yeah.
totally incapable of having that
routine. So, this is like a nice forcing
function.
Absolutely.
Look at the month and see what else has
happened.
And And it's always great to talk to so
many amazing people. We've got some
We've got some interesting sessions
lined up as well. I had a session a
little while ago with Laurent Tau. Going
to continue that kind of like security
theme into next month. And we had some
good We had some good fun. Who else have
we got? Oh, we've got Patrick Dubois.
He's the Is he the godfather or the
father or the grandfather or something
uncle or something of of DevOps?
You should you should try a grandfather.
I'm sure he'll
Grandfather. Yeah, grand the great
grandfather of DevOps.
Definitely the creator of DevOps days
and I think a big big big force in
making DevOps and kind of that
development come to life.
Yeah.
Yeah, looking forward to chatting a
little bit about how
So, you're going to be chatting with
Patrick later today. And And you're
going to be talking about the
similarities between the cloud push and
the DevOps push. How we can create
reflections and similarities between
that and AI native. What can we What we
can expect if it follows the same path?
That's going to be That's going to be a
very interesting discussion. I'm looking
forward to that.
forward to it. I think cloud native is
such a great role model for AI native.
Yeah.
And I think to me like following DevOps
and cloud natives was also very
significant in Snyk. We didn't coin a
catchphrase that for security. It's not
a There's no native in it. Security
native conversation that I don't think
it was as big a change on it. I think
these lessons were so valuable in making
Snyk work, you know, and uh and how how
do we embed security to development and
so I'm keen to see how do we learn from
those journeys and from you know,
Patrick's wisdom
and apply that to AI natives so
Yeah. So Guy, let's catch up in a month
and we'll talk through some of these
amazing sessions again.
I'll try to ignore you for
Yeah, absolutely. If I'm still here,
we'll see how that HR
You might have another co-host.
Maybe Ben will be back before we
realize.
It's a good idea. I'll take problem
solved.
Excellent. So Guy, we'll see you next
month and in the meantime I'll be on
LinkedIn looking for work.
Thanks all for listening. See you next
time.
Thanks for tuning in. Join us next time
on the AI Native Dev brought to you by
Tesler.